Tanner Muldoon

300 Alexander St Apt 303 Rochester, NY, 14607

U.S. Citizen

tannermuldoon@gmail.com 404-834-4699 www.linkedin.com/in/ tanner-muldoon-b3a587165

I'm a software engineer with 5+ years professional experience, 15+ years personal experience. I have sizeable experience in real-time, interactive software, with most of my career focusing on embedded systems engineering, including embedded Linux. I also have a long history as a hobbyist developing video games, and I've dabbled in full-stack development. I'm highly comfortable working on both maintenance of existing or legacy features and design of entirely new features from scratch.

Education and Certifications

Georgia Institute of Technology | Atlanta, GA

Bachelors of Science in Computer Engineering, GPA 3.74

June 2016 — May 2019

• Graduated with Highest Honors

Scrum Master Certification (SMC)

Scrum Alliance December 2020

Work Experience

L3Harris Technologies | Rochester, NY

Specialist, Software Engineering Sr. Associate, Software Engineering

March 2023 — Present

March 2021 — March 2023

Associate, Software Engineering

June 2019 — March 2021

L3Harris is a leading provider of tactical radios, with customers in 100 countries

- Subject matter expert (SME) in digital signal processing (DSP)
- Provided technical leadership and design contributions on 5+ distinct products
- Key role as a "jack of all trades" able to work in areas where little technical knowledge exists within the company

Georgia Tech Research Institute | Atlanta, GA

Student Research Assistant

May 2018 — August 2018

Electronic Systems Lab (ELSYS) specializes primarily in electronic warfare

• Developed a proxy server to convert realtime image data from a backend simulator (OpenEaagles) to API calls for an external frontend program (Prepar3D)

Georgia Institute of Technology | Atlanta, GA

Head Teaching Assistant

Teaching Assistant

August 2018 — May 2019

January 2018 — May 2019

Systems and Networks is an intro computer architecture and operating systems course, typically with 250-300 students

• Managed a team of 12 TAs, handling administrative overhead and supervising the creation and grading of assignments

Personal Projects

LVL: Labyrinthine Variable Landscape

Independent Video Game

October 2020 — January 2023 (Hiatus)

• Unity video game utilizing several difficult concepts such as procedural generation of levels, character AI, and automatic testing

Schmappling Hook: Subsistence

48-Hour Game Jam

January 2021

• Made in Unity over a 48 hour period by a team of Georgia Tech students and alumni

VGMQ: Video Game Music Quiz

In-Browser Video Game

September 2020 — October 2020

• Full-stack development in Node is to create a game for guessing the source of random video game songs